[Music]
Hi, my name is Julia and I'm here today
with Eritton to talk to you about what's
new in Copilot Chat.
This wave in Copilot Chat, we see big
enhancements. Now, Copilot can answer
users question using documentation from
installed thirdparty add-ons, meaning
that it broadened it knowledge from just
Microsoft learn to now also partners uh
partner and other installed
applications.
It works out of the box with only one
step setup enabling Bing search. No
extra configuration needed. Copilot then
automatically searches relevant partner
extension documentation to support
users. Users can now on board faster,
get unblocked quicker, and make smarter
decisions. All thanks to improved out
ofthe-box copilot experience.
So let's see what changed. As you can
see here, I have an extension installed
called fabric project management. So
let's ask copilot chat what is fabric
and project management.
As you can see with previous experience
copilot chat could not find the answers
to questions about something that wasn't
uh Microsoft or wasn't documented in
Microsoft learn documentation.
But now administrators can enable bing
search on the copilot and agent
capabilities page. So if I were to
enable it, Erton, can you show us how
that story would look like?
>> Okay, so now that we've enabled Bing
search, let's try that search again. Um,
and hopefully we'll get some answers
about the extension that Julia has
installed. So what is Fabricam
project management?
Brilliant. So we can see this time that
I get an answer. Fabric and project
management adds lightweight project task
resource pool roll and allocation
management to Dynamics 365 Business
Central. And you might be wondering
where did this answer come from. So now
if I check the references, we can see
instead of the usual Microsoft learn
sources, we see a Fabricom project
management source with the icon of the
extension. And when I click through to
this, it's going to take me to
Fabricom's website. Um and we can see on
the website it says fabric and project
management as lightweight task project
resource pool and allocation management
to dynamics 365 business central. So the
content that was in the copilot chat
answer was pulled directly from this
website content. So now let's get
started using this extension. I want to
create a project so that Julia can work
on it. So the first question I'm going
to ask is how do I create a project?
So just like with normal copilot chat
when it answers questions on Microsoft
learn I get detailed list of steps
instructing me on how to perform this
task and those steps are also drawn from
the partner website. You can see in the
bottom of this answer it says powered by
Bing and that's because the results that
power these answers are pulled directly
from the Bing search index. So now if I
was to go to bing.com and search for how
do I create a project in fabric and
project management
then we can see the search result here
and when I click this it takes me to the
partner website. So as of release wave 2
now um copilot chat will be able to draw
content from the bing index. Cool. So
let's try to follow these steps and see
how far we get.
So if I type in fabric projects
and now I can create a new project.
And step three says select a project
template to apply a default budget and
duration. So I'm going to select a
template code. And you can see that it's
filled in the budget amount. And I would
continue to fill out these fields until
I get stuck on pool code. What does pool
code mean? But I can ask Copilot Chat
this question too. So now let's ask what
is the pool code field for?
So we can see the answer here. The pool
code field links the project to a
default resource pool for the planning
context. And if I click through to this
page, I can see the app's reference
content which gives more detailed
information about how different fields
work. Um, this is an example of how you
can provide targeted help content to
address users commonly asked questions
so that they can be unblocked by
co-pilot without having to contact your
custom support line. So, finally, I
would like to assign readonly access to
these projects to Julia so that she can
see what everybody is working on. So,
now I'm going to ask um what permissions
do I need to assign to users to grant
read only access to projects.
So we can see in copilot's answer that I
need to assign the FPM project viewer
permission set. So finally I'm going to
click through to this source and I can
see that copilot has drawn this answer
from which content this table is on this
page. So you can format the content in a
way that is readable for users on your
website. But copilot chat is also going
to be able to pick up this content to
surface answers within the product. And
for more information about how to
prepare your content, you can see other
sessions on our YouTube channel.
>> So remember, starting this wave,
administrators can turn on enable Bing
search switch on copilot and agent
capabilities page to get this enabled
out of the box. It will work for
automatically for apps source extensions
that had provided link to their
documentation. And if you install a PTE
extension, you have to provide that uh
documentation as well within the help
URL. Let's spend a moment addressing
some common questions about a Bing
search and copilot chat. Is it safe?
Inputs and outputs go through various
checks for safety both from security
standpoint and uh to reduce risks of AI
harms. Copilot can connect to the web.
However, the web cannot connect to the
copilot.
So where does my data go? The Bing
service is in the US and the data is uh
goes to there and is not stored for
longer than a day. What is passed to
Bing search is a curated search terms uh
derived from the user query to our
copilot chat. Does it cost more at this
point? Using Bing Search within Copilot
Chat does not cost more and you do not
incur any one-time or service costs when
using Bing Search within Copilot Chat in
Business Central. So that's it from us
and you can watch more videos on our
YouTube channel to learn more both how
to prepare your content and about other
awesome things that are coming this
wave. Thank you for watching.
>> Thank you.